<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Web on Igor Zubko</title>
    <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/tags/web/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Web on Igor Zubko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 23:52:43 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/tags/web/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirrow.me</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 23:52:43 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirrow.me&lt;/strong&gt; is a newly released app built for fashionista’s of all sorts. This app is straightforward to use allowing you to store, and show off your wardrobe to the community within the app. By uploading your clothing styles the app will start to suggest similar style of clothing that may suit you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ForeclosureCanada</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 18:42:59 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bank foreclosures are properties that have defaulted on their mortgage payments and are re-possessed by the bank. In order to recover their loan as soon as possible, banks sell foreclosures often at massive discounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These incredible deals go fast, so investors or homebuyers with the most updated information have the buying advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this app, this advantage is now yours!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find all types of realtor properties throughout canada. Alberta, British Columbia, Ontario, Manitoba, Saskatchewan, Nova Scotia. New Brunswick, Quebec and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also find single-family homes, condos, townhomes, apartments, commercial properties, raw land and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also find estate sales, probate sales, tax sales, motivated sellers, and many other types of properties that sell for below market value!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>