<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio on Igor Zubko</title>
    <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/categories/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolio on Igor Zubko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 23:52:43 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/categories/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mirrow.me</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/8/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 23:52:43 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mirrow.me&lt;/strong&gt; is a newly released app built for fashionista’s of all sorts. This app is straightforward to use allowing you to store, and show off your wardrobe to the community within the app. By uploading your clothing styles the app will start to suggest similar style of clothing that may suit you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FitnesTainer</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/7/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 23:29:48 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fitness Trainer&lt;/strong&gt; is a exercise app designed to be the only tool you need other than yourself in the gym or at home. The first class Fitness Trainer app brings you everything you need to know about working out with tons of other features that make it far superior than any other fitness app.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MortgageCalc</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/5/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 19:04:45 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With &lt;strong&gt;MortgageCalc&lt;/strong&gt; you can easily calculate monthly payments on mortgage rates and other loans.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AbTrainerX</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 18:57:13 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Have your very own personal trainer at your fingertips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use the &lt;strong&gt;AbTrainerX&lt;/strong&gt; app on your iphone every other day for 30 days. It is about a 10 min ab work out&amp;hellip;so not a big time commitment!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ForeclosureCanada</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 18:42:59 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bank foreclosures are properties that have defaulted on their mortgage payments and are re-possessed by the bank. In order to recover their loan as soon as possible, banks sell foreclosures often at massive discounts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These incredible deals go fast, so investors or homebuyers with the most updated information have the buying advantage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this app, this advantage is now yours!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find all types of realtor properties throughout canada. Alberta, British Columbia, Ontario, Manitoba, Saskatchewan, Nova Scotia. New Brunswick, Quebec and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also find single-family homes, condos, townhomes, apartments, commercial properties, raw land and more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also find estate sales, probate sales, tax sales, motivated sellers, and many other types of properties that sell for below market value!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ZombieWrack</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 18:15:14 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Disable all traps, throwing zombies into them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aztec Run</title>
      <link>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 16:44:36 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kirkfawkes.github.io/portfolio/post/1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aztec Run&lt;/strong&gt; is a simple and fun falling game.
Enjoy playing the old-fashioned but still addictive gameplay.
Imagine yourself a golden ball jumping from one platform to another trying not to crash.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game has two control options. Use arrows or tilt to surf through platforms, trying not to hit the spikes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>